Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Public Relations Department records 1962-1967 IBT0030
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Public Relations Department Records
1962-1967
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0030
1.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains correspondence, clippings, and photos for possible use in The International Teamster. Some letters are to James R. Hoffa, some to Harold Gibbons or to Allen Biggs (Director of Public Relations). 1962-1967.
Arrangement
Organized into 1 series: Research Materials For Teamsters News
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2013 [2012.056].
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, clippings, and photos for possible use in The International Teamster, the official magazine of the IBT. The collection includes letters to James R. Hoffa, Harold Gibbons, and Director of Public Relations Allen Biggs.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Publications; Labor unions; Labor; Public relations; Research
- Research Materials For Teamsters News, 1962-1967; Series 1; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged in original order
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, clippings, and photos for possible use in The International Teamster. Some letters are to James R. Hoffa, some to Harold Gibbons or to Allen Biggs (Director of Public Relations), dating from 1962-1967.
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [1 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [2 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [3 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [4 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [5 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [6 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [7 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [8 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [9 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [10 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [11 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [12 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [13 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [14 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [15 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [16 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [17 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [18 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Research Materials Teamsters News [19 of 19], 1962-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)